turners.com 2017-02-10

# Privacy Policy | Turner’s Outdoorsman

Last Updated: September 30, 2013

**General Information**  
This privacy policy explains how we use the personal information collected on this site. Please read this privacy policy before using the site or submitting any personal information. By using the site, you are accepting the practices described in this privacy policy. These practices may be changed, but any changes will be posted. You are encouraged to review the privacy policy whenever you visit the site to make sure that you understand how any personal information you provide will be used.

Note, the privacy practices set forth in this privacy policy are for this web site only. If you link to other web sites, please review the privacy policies posted at those sites.

Turner’s Outdoorsman will always respect the privacy of our customers. We want to give the best customer service possible. The only information we collect is the information given when an order is placed. At no time will we sell or share that information with any other company. The information obtained from registration on-line is used to save you time in the future and /or receive occasional e-mails. By using our site, you consent to our online policy.

**Collection of Information**  
When you order from us, we collect your name, billing address, shipping address, email address, phone number. We also gather information on the person who will receive any gift you send (e.g. that person's name address and phone number) and we will retain a record of your purchases.  When you become a turners.com registered user, we collect your name, mailing address, email address, phone number, username and password. This information is gathered to make your shopping experience as a registered user as quick and easy as possible. At any time you may log-in to our 'Member Log-In' Section, and update any of this information. As well as track order status. We do not store your credit card information on file.  When you enter a contest online, we collect you name, address, email address, and phone number. We also may ask you for additional information, such as your age, interests and product preferences.  When you submit a question to customer service, we will need your email address to respond and you will have to provide us with additional information to help us answer your question. For example you may need to include your First and Last name, email address, and invoice number.

**Use of Information**  
We collect personally identifiable information, like names, postal addresses, email addresses, etc., when voluntarily submitted by our visitors. The information you provide is used to fulfill your specific request. Any of the information we collect from you may be used in one of the following ways:

  1. To improve customer service (your information helps us to more effectively respond to your customer service requests and support needs)
  2. To process transactions
  3. Your information, whether public or private, will not be sold, exchanged, transferred, or given to any other company for any reason whatsoever, without your consent, other than for the express purpose of delivering the purchased product or service requested.
  4. To send emails and catalogs
  5. The email address you provide for order processing, may be used to send you information and updates pertaining to your order, in addition to receiving occasional company news, updates, related product or service information, etc.

Note: If at any time you would like to unsubscribe from receiving future emails, we include detailed unsubscribe instructions at the bottom of each email.

**Minors**  
Turners Outdoorsman does sell products for children, but it does not sell products to children. You must be at least 18 years old to have our permission to use the Sites. Our policy is that we do not knowingly collect or permit the collection, storage, use or disclosure of Personally Identifiable Information about visitors who are under 18 years of age. If you are a parent or guardian who knows or has discovered that your child under the age of 18 has submitted his or her Personally Identifiable Information or other information without your consent, permission or authorization, please notify “Privacy Support” by e-mail or by letter to:

Turner’s Outdoorsman  
Attention: Privacy Support  
11738 San Marino St. Suite A  
Rancho Cucamonga, California 91730

Upon receiving such a notice, we will take steps to: (a) notify you what information may have been used and/or disclosed; and (b) remove your child’s Personally Identifiable Information or other information from our databases, cease the use of such information, and direct any other party with access to such information to do the same.

**Sharing of Information**  
We may share information with governmental agencies or other companies assisting us in fraud prevention or investigation. We may do so when: (1) permitted or required by law; or, (2) trying to protect against or prevent actual or potential fraud or unauthorized transactions; or, (3) investigating fraud which has already taken place. The information is not provided to these companies for marketing purposes.

**Social Sharing Features**  
The Services may offer social sharing features or other integrated tools, which let you share actions you take on the Services with other media, and vice versa.  The use of such features enables the sharing of information with your friends or the public, depending on the settings you establish with the third party that provides the social sharing feature.  For more information about the purpose and scope of data collection and processing in connection with social sharing features, please visit the privacy policies of the third parties that provide these features.

**Security**  
We use Secure Socket Layer (SSL) technology to encrypt important information, such as your credit card data, in an effort to prevent unauthorized access during transmission of your orders over the Internet. We incorporate standard industry practices internally and with our service providers suitable to the degree of sensitivity of the information involved to maintain the security of your personal information and to avoid its disclosure except as described in this policy. Your personal information may also be protected by the password you created when you register at our website where this feature is offered. The confidentiality of any password is yours to protect. You may change it anytime by following the instructions at the website where you registered.

Although we use our best efforts to assure that your data remains secure when maintained by us, security during Internet transmissions cannot be assured due to possible security vulnerabilities on your computer. We limit access to personal data only to those Turner’s Outdoorsman employees or agents with a specific need to access or retrieve this information. We store data on multiple service systems, in controlled, secure environments.

Your personally identifiable information is kept secure. Only authorized employees, agents and contractors (who have agreed to keep information secure and confidential) have access to this information.

**Your Choices**  
You may update or correct information about you by logging into your online account or calling Customer Service. You may also email us if you wish to deactivate your account, but note that we may retain information about you for legitimate business purposes or as required by law.

You may opt out of receiving promotional emails and text messages from Turner’s Outdoorsman by following the instructions in those communications or changing your preferences via http://www.turners.com/myaccount/home. If you opt out of receiving promotional communications, we may still send you non-promotional emails, such as emails about your purchases, account, or our ongoing business relations.

**Third Party Advertising, Analytics and Services**  
The Site may use cookie and tracking technology depending on the features offered. Cookie and tracking technology are useful for gathering information such as browser type and operating system, tracking the number of visitors to the Site, and understanding how visitors use the Site. Cookies can also help customize the Site for visitors. Personal information cannot be collected via cookies and other tracking technology; however, if you previously provided personally identifiable information, cookies may be tied to such information. Aggregate cookie and tracking information may be shared with third parties.

**Your California Privacy Rights**  
If you are a California resident, in addition to the rights set forth above, you have the right to request information from us regarding the manner in which we share certain categories of your personal information with third parties, for the third parties' direct marketing purposes. California law provides that you have the right to submit a request to us at the designated address and receive the following information:

  1. The categories of information we disclosed to third parties for the third parties direct marketing purposes during the preceding calendar year.
  2. The names and addresses of third parties that received such information: and if the nature of a third party's business cannot be reasonably determined from the third party's name, examples of the products or services marketed.

You are entitled to receive a copy of this information in a standardized format and the information will not be specific to you individually. Please send you requests via e-mail to privacy support.

**Changes to this Policy**  
Turner’s Outdoorsman may change this Policy from time to time. If we make changes, we will notify you by revising the Last Updated above and, in some cases we may provide you with more prominent notice. We encourage you to review the Policy to stay informed about our information practices and the ways you can help protect your privacy.

**Contact Us**  
If you have any questions, concerns, or comments about our privacy policy you may contact us using the information below:

By E-Mail

Turner’s Outdoorsman  
Attention: Privacy Support  
11738 San Marino St. Suite A  
Rancho Cucamonga, CA 91730

We reserve the right to make changes to this policy. Any changes to this policy will be posted.
